http://www.maine.gov/portal/policies/privacy.html

Privacy Policy
Visitors to the Maine.gov website are important to us. Maine.gov does not record personal information about you without your permission. Maine.gov collects only the information needed to create an efficient electronic gateway for public information. State agencies may have their own privacy statements posted on their sites. Those statements will over-ride this policy only if they provide greater protection to you.
Collection of Information
Maine.gov automatically collects some information when you look or search through our web pages.
It is collected for statistical purposes only. We use the information to make our site easier to use.
We do not use it to identify you personally. The information collected includes the following:
The date and time of your visit.
Information about your browser type and operating system.
The parts of our web site you visited.
The Internet address of your computer and the site that sent you to us.
If you used a search page to find us, the search terms you entered.
Maine.gov does not ever automatically collect information like your name, address, e-mail address, or phone number. Be aware that in order to complete some services you may need to provide personal information. Supplying this information is voluntary. We do not use or place spyware on your computer.
E-mail
E-mail sent to Maine.gov may be stored for a time. This will allow us to respond to the request, forward it to the appropriate agency, or to provide valuable feedback to help improve the website. Please be aware that under Maine law, e-mail addresses are public records and as such are subject to inspection by the public.
Online Forms
Any information you supply during the completion of an online form will be considered voluntary.
This information will be treated the same as any provided in person during a visit to the agency. It may be necessary to share this information with another state agency for proper handling.
Cookies
Maine.gov uses cookies for certain types of online services. Cookies are small text files set by a website and stored by your web browser and sent back to the website when you visit again. Cookies also store information provided by you and facilitate complex and customized services. Your browser’s "help" feature will tell you how to disable cookies. Cookies allow you to take advantage of many online services. We advise you to set your web browser to use them.
Cookies allow us to make complex online services easier for you to use. We use them to save you the trouble of retyping information already provided. We also use them to track your progress while a transaction is in process. When used this way, the cookie is deleted when you leave the website.
Cookies also allow us to provide customized services. In these cases, without storing sensitive data, a cookie is permanently stored on your web browser that lets you view web pages customized by you on earlier visits and provide us statistics about repeat visits.
Subscribers
Some visitors subscribe to special services through an InforME subscription account. Information provided during sign up is used to manage accounts. These records are confidential. They will only be released with subscriber’s written permission.
Public Disclosure
Unless specifically protected under federal or state law, any information provided may be inspected by the public or disclosed. Please refer to 1 MRSA Chapter 13 for more information on public records and under what circumstances it is released.
Incorrect Information
Information presented on the Maine.gov site is done on the behalf of state agencies. If you find something that is out of date or wrong please contact the agency or Maine.gov webmaster. Do not include any sensitive data, such as your personal information, when you contact us to correct data inaccuracies. The secure transfer of this type of information will be arranged later if necessary.
Contact Information
To offer comments about the Maine.gov website or this Privacy Statement, contact the Maine.gov webmaster.
Copyright © 2017 All rights reserved.
